

jmweber5@gmail.com 812-573-7227 LinkedIn

ABOUT

I am an effective web developer that has extensive team-based, independent deadline experience. I have both formal and self-taught education, and am aiming to be a front-end developer with a focus in the design and visual aspects.

SKILLS

WEB

Website Design	Agile/Git Teams/Scrum	Final Cut X	Edius
Javascript/jQuery	PHP	After Effects	Lightroom
HTML5 / CSS3	API	Premiere Pro	Pinnacle Studio
React.js/React Legac	cy Wordpress	Photoshop	GIMP
Node.js	Bootstrap/Reactstrap/Flexbox	Illustrator	Professional Photograph
TypeScript	Visual Studio (light experience)	Adobe XD	Cinematography
Heroku & Firebase	Python (light experience)	InDesign	Corel Video Studio

VISUAL

PROJECTS

MEGAMOVIES

November, 2020

React and Node.js based project created for Eleven Fifty Academy. I designed the site using Adobe XD, created the logos, layout, and colorscheme. I also created the GET and DELETE functions and the More Info section.

CJT FILMS

July, 2020

HTML5, CSS, and PHP based project created for local freelance group. Designed the site using Illustrator, and with partner created the site from scratch.

CERTIFICATIONS

GOLD BADGE/BLUE BADGE/RED BADGE WEB DEVELOPMENT

Eleven Fifty Academy

WEB DESIGNER & WEB DEVELOPER COURSE Udemy

UI & WEB DESIGN USING ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

RESPONSIVE DESIGN HTML CSS WEB DESIGN

EDUCATION

ELEVEN FIFTY ACADEMY

October, 2020 - January, 2021

12-week full time learning program for Web Development. Up-to-date industry standards, real-world based projects, 500+ hours of logged coding time and training.

IVY TECH COMMUNITY COLLEGE

January, 2020 - Present

Web Application Development Certification. Taking two 8-week classes a semester to learn web design, Python, Visual Studio, and general web development.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE VIDEO EDITOR

ZERGNET

May and June, 2020

Remotely edited video content for multi-million subscriber channels, such as Looper and Nicki Swift. Used Premiere Pro and After Effects to create a consistent product

VIDEO EDITOR

FOX59/CBS4

November, 2016 - December 2019

Worked under strict deadlines with a team to create videos for daily newscasts. I communicated with show creators to ensure that everyone was on the same page and fulfilled requests to expectations.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER/VIDEO EDITOR

14 NEWS/WFIE

September 2014 - October 2016

Used Photoshop and LyricX to create graphics for daily newscasts. I also rotated between master control, audio boards, cameras, and directing. I brought in my own camera and audio equipment to create promotional material.

CASHIER/CLEANER/USHER

SHOWPLACE CINEMAS NEWBURGH

June, 2011 - October, 2016

PHOTOGRAPHER

PRESTIGE PHOTOGRAPHY

August, 2014 - November, 2014